- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
♪ ♪
- [imitates engine revving]
- [模仿发动机转速]
I'm a stunt driver,
and I'm making donuts!
我是一名特技车手
我正在做甜甜圈！
[screeches]
Out of the way!
[尖叫声]
让开！
[screeches]
Look out!
[尖叫声]
当心！
Where'd you learn
to drive, buddy?
你在哪里学的
开车吗，伙计？
Oh, Mrs. Puff's
Boating School?
哦，泡芙夫人的
划船学校？
Me too!
[laughs]
我也是！
[笑]
Ahh, the bridge is out!
啊啊，桥出来了！
Ahhh!
啊啊！
- That's a sweet little boat.
- 那是一艘可爱的小船。
You're a smart shopper.
您是一位聪明的购物者。
- Oh, I'm not shopping.
I'm playing.
- 哦，我不购物。
我正在玩。
- Playing, huh?
- 玩，嗯？
Well, we have some very
playful items here for a--a...
嗯，我们有一些非常
这里有一些有趣的物品，适合...
- Ehh-ehh.
- 呃呃。
- ...sophisticated motorist
like yourself.
- ...老练的驾驶者
就像你自己一样。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- The Nerdmobile.
- 书呆子车。
It comes with
pocket protectors,
它配备了
口袋保护器，
corrective lens windshield
and seat wedgies.
矫正镜片挡风玻璃
和座椅楔子。
- Ah-ow! Wow.
- No, this isn't right.
- 啊-哦！哇。
- 不，这是不对的。
I got something
more your style.
我得到了一些东西
更符合你的风格。
- Whee!
- 呼！
- The Wimp Wagon.
- 懦夫马车。
It includes unlimited tissues
for crying,
它包括无限的组织
因为哭泣，
a security blanket,
安全毯，
and a bumper bonnet for your
delicate fontanel.
以及为您准备的保险杠引擎盖
娇嫩的囟门。
- Oh, these are very nice,
- 哦，这些非常好，
but I don't have
a driver's license.
但我没有
驾驶执照。
- No license, huh?
- 没有执照，是吧？
Well, you don't need a license
嗯，你不需要许可证
to drive a self-driving boat.
驾驶自动驾驶船。
- Self-driving?
[whimpers]
- 自驾？
[呜咽]
- Meet Coupe.
It's very classy.
- 认识一下轿跑车。
这是非常优雅的。
Chrome-plated exterior,
titanium hubcaps,
外部镀铬，
钛合金轮毂盖，
turbine engine,
涡轮发动机,
and personal driver narration.
以及个人司机解说。
- Ooh.
Whaaa!
- 哦。
哇啊！
Sold!
卖！
- Oh, thanks.
[laughs]
-哦，谢谢。
[笑]
- Ahhh!
My very own boat.
- 啊啊！
我自己的船。
Ah!
啊!
Huh?
But there's no key!
啊？
但没有钥匙！
And no steering wheel!
而且没有方向盘！
[stammering]
Where is that--I gotta--
[结巴]
那在哪里——我得——
[cat meows]
[猫喵喵叫]
How do you--
你怎么——
- Settle down,
Mr. SquarePants.
- 安定下来，
方裤先生。
- Wow, you talk.
How'd you know my name?
- 哇，你说话了。
你怎么知道我的名字？
- I can feel your
square pants on my seat.
- 我能感觉到你的
方裤在我的座位上。
Where to, Mr. SquarePants?
去哪儿，方裤先生？
- Oh, why don't we just
go for a drive?
-哦，我们为什么不直接
开车去兜风吗？
- You've got it.
- 你明白了。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Whoa, careful!
哇，小心点！
And stay in your lane!
Stop sign! Stop sign!
并留在你的车道上！
停止标志！停止标志！
Truck, truck, truck, truck.
Ahh!
卡车，卡车，卡车，卡车。
啊！
- Relax, Mr. SquarePants.
- 放松点，方裤先生。
I'm an expert driver.
我是一名专业司机。
Make yourself at home
and leave everything to me.
让自己像在家一样
并把一切都交给我。
- Hmm. Huh?
[horn honks]
- 唔。啊？
[喇叭鸣响]
- Hi, Squidward.
- 嗨，章鱼哥。
[instrument blares,
horn honks]
[乐器声，
喇叭鸣响]
- Oh, I need to erase this
from my mind.
- 哦，我需要删除这个
从我的脑海中。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Duh!
What's a SpongeBob?
呃！
什么是海绵宝宝？
- Oh, hi, Mrs. Puff.
- 哦，嗨，帕芙女士。
What do you think
of my classy new boat?
你觉得怎么样
我的优雅新船？
- Hello, SpongeBob.
- 你好，海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob, ah!
海绵宝宝啊！
You're not driving.
你没开车。
- I know.
Isn't it great?
- 我知道。
不是很好吗？
[horn blares]
- Ahhh!
[喇叭声]
- 啊啊！
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Oh, that was the best day
of non-driving ever.
- 哦，那是最好的一天
从未驾驶过。
Coupe, is there anything
I can get you?
轿跑车，有什么吗
我可以得到你吗？
Warm glass of oil?
Triple-foam conditioner?
温杯油吗？
三重泡沫护发素？
- I'm fine.
Good night, Mr. SquarePants.
- 我很好。
晚安，方裤先生。
- Good night, Coupe.
- 晚安，库珀。
[thunder rumbles]
[雷声隆隆]
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
What's wrong, Coupe?
怎么了，库珀？
- I'm getting wet.
- 我被淋湿了。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Here, take this!
给，拿着这个！
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
What's up?
- I'm cold.
这是怎么回事？
- 我很冷。
- Aww.
- 哇。
There you go,
my widdle self-driver.
就这样吧，
我的自驾游。
Nice and snuggy-wuggy.
漂亮又舒适。
- I don't like it out here.
I want to be inside.
- 我不喜欢这里。
我想呆在里面。
- Inside?
- 里面？
[sawing]
[锯切]
All right, Coupe.
Come on in.
好吧，库珀。
进来吧。
[woman screaming on TV,
engine revving]
[女人在电视上尖叫，
发动机转速]
[dinosaurs growling,
monster growling]
[恐龙咆哮，
怪物咆哮]
- Hey, you know what'd be fun?
- 嘿，你知道什么有趣吗？
If I sat in you
and we pretended
如果我坐在你身边
我们假装
we were in a drive-in movie.
我们在看一场汽车电影院。
- No, it wouldn't.
- 不，不会的。
- Okay, so I guess you're
just gonna click through
- 好吧，所以我猜你是
只需点击即可
the channels looking for a boat
commercial all night, huh?
寻找船只的海峡
通宵做广告吧？
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- 哦，对不起。
I thought I was a guest here.
我以为我是这里的客人。
- Of course you are.
- 当然是。
Well, I'm tired.
You can stay up.
好吧，我累了。
你可以熬夜。
I'm going to bed.
我要去睡觉了。
Oh, Coupe?
哦，轿跑车？
Good-night.
I had a wonderful day.
晚安。
我度过了美好的一天。
[sounds from
television continue]
[声音来自
电视继续]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Ohh!
- Ow.
哦！
- 噢。
- Gary, what is what?
- 加里，什么是什么？
[hyperventilating]
[换气过度]
[horn blares]
[喇叭声]
- Sorry, Mr. SquarePants,
I'm so...[yawns]
- 对不起，方裤先生，
我真是……[哈欠]
- I know, Coupe.
- 我知道，库普。
You're tired.
We're all tired.
你累了。
我们都累了。
[horn blaring rhythmically]
[有节奏的喇叭声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
[horn continues blaring]
[喇叭继续鸣响]
[both snoring]
[两人都打呼噜]
[horn blares, both scream]
[喇叭声，两人尖叫]
Ow.
噢。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- Mr. SquarePants,
I can drive you to work.
- 方裤先生，
我可以开车送你去上班。
Why are you walking?
你为什么走路？
- Oh, yeah, well,
I didn't want to wake you.
- 哦，是的，好吧，
我不想吵醒你。
You were sleeping like a baby.
你睡得像个婴儿。
Heh. Baby buggy!
[laughs] Baby buggy...
呵呵。婴儿车！
[笑] 婴儿车...
- Hey SpongeBob,
how about a ride?
- 嘿海绵宝宝，
搭车怎么样？
- Well, sure, Patrick.
Hop in.
- 嗯，当然，帕特里克。
跳进去。
- Yay!
- 耶！
[horn blares]
[喇叭声]
Oh, oh boy!
噢，天哪！
Buttons!
按钮！
[laughing]
[笑]
- Patrick, could you not--
- 帕特里克，你能不能——
I don't think he--
Don't get your--
我不认为他——
别明白你的——
- Butt on buttons!
- 按下按钮！
- Uh, Patrick, I don't think
Coupe likes that.
- 呃，帕特里克，我不认为
轿跑车喜欢这样。
- Passenger, settle down.
- 乘客，安定下来。
- Hey, ice cream.
Where's the cone?
- 嘿，冰淇淋。
圆锥体在哪里？
- Oh, don't worry.
It's down there somewhere.
- 哦，别担心。
它就在下面某个地方。
Ahh.
啊。
[excited grunting]
[兴奋的咕噜声]
[Coupe groans, spits]
[轿跑车呻吟，吐口水]
[excited grunting]
[兴奋的咕噜声]
- Ugh, Eww.
All right, that's enough!
- 呃，呃。
好吧，够了！
- Thanks for the ride!
- 感谢您的搭车！
- Here we are.
- 我们到了。
- Here we are, where?
- 我们在这里，在哪里？
- Where I work,
the Krusty Krab.
- 我工作的地方，
蟹堡王。
- What?
I can't be seen here.
- 什么？
我在这里看不见。
I'm a classy car.
我是一辆高级车。
This place is tacky.
[flatulence sound]
这个地方很俗气。
[胀气声]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Coupe, open the door!
I'll be late.
轿跑车，开门！
我会迟到的。
Yow!
But I have to go to work!
哟！
但我还得去上班！
Ah.
啊。
- You obviously
have no taste,
- 显然你
没有品味，
so today we're going to do
what I want to do.
所以今天我们要做
我想做的事。
- But I have to go to work.
[groans]
- 但我必须去上班。
[呻吟]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[gargling]
[漱口]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
I have to go to work.
我得去上班了。
[tools whirring, clanging]
[工具发出呼呼声、叮当声]
But I have to go to work!
但我还得去上班！
Huh?
[cash register dings]
啊？
[收银机叮叮声]
Ugh.
啊。
I have to go--
- Go to work?
我得走了——
- 去上班吗？
- No, go to the bathroom.
- 不，去趟洗手间。
- You can hold it.
- 你可以握住它。
- Or I could just go.
[fly unzips]
- 或者我可以走。
[飞拉开拉链]
- Ugh. Make it snappy.
- 呃。让它变得活泼。
- Ow!
[groans]
- 噢！
[呻吟]
- Hmm?
Hmm.
- 唔？
唔。
Hmm.
- Eh?
[whistles]
- 呃？
[口哨声]
[tense music]
[紧张的音乐]
Hmm.
[stammering]
唔。
[结巴]
Very funny, Coupe.
Very funny.
非常有趣，库珀。
很搞笑。
- What's in the bag?
- Oh, nothing.
- 包里有什么？
- 哦，没什么。
Hey, wait!
嘿，等等！
- What are you doing,
SquarePants?
- 你在做什么，
方裤？
- I'm going to work.
- 我要去工作了。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[tires screeching]
- Ooh.
[轮胎的尖叫声]
- 哦。
- Did that hurt?
- Of course not.
- 疼吗？
- 当然不是。
I'm a boat.
I don't feel physical pain.
我是一条船。
我感觉不到身体上的疼痛。
- Good to know,
because I'm a stunt driver,
- 很高兴知道，
因为我是一名特技车手
and I'm making donuts.
我正在做甜甜圈。
[Coupe screaming]
[轿跑车尖叫]
- Oh, no you don't.
- 哦，不，你不知道。
Give me that!
给我那个！
- Yahh!
- Ohh!
- 呀！
- 哦！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
[Coupe laughs]
[轿跑车笑]
Now this is where
I should be living.
现在这是哪里
我应该活着。
Penthouse parking lot,
please.
顶层公寓停车场，
请。
[ding]
Thank you.
[叮]
谢谢你。
- Hi, how you doing today?
Good?
- 嗨，你今天过得怎么样？
好的？
[whistles]
[口哨声]
[tropical music]
[热带音乐]
Well played, Coupe.
- Indeed.
打得好，库珀。
- 的确。
- And now we can get to
the Krusty Krab the fast way!
- 现在我们可以到达
蟹堡王的快捷方式！
- What? No! No!
Noooo!
- 什么？不！不！
不！
No, you don't.
- [straining]
不，你不知道。
- [紧张]
- No, no, we're not going
into the tacky Krusty Krab.
- 不，不，我们不会去
进入俗气的蟹堡王。
- You're right, we're going
through the drive-thru!
- 你说得对，我们要去
通过驾车穿过！
Triple Krabby Patty with five
scoops of ice cream please.
三重蟹肉饼与五个
请给我几勺冰淇淋。
[straining]
[紧张]
Squidward, you see me
struggling with this boat,
章鱼哥，你看见我了
与这艘船苦苦挣扎，
and you act like
you don't care.
你表现得像
你不在乎。
- It's not an act.
- 这不是一种行为。
- I hate do you this to you,
- 我讨厌这样对你，
Triple Krabby Patty
with five scoops of ice cream,
三重蟹肉饼
配上五勺冰淇淋，
but I have no choice.
但我别无选择。
- Oh, no, stop!
I don't like that.
- 哦，不，停下来！
我不喜欢这样。
[tires screech]
- Hey, SpongeBob!
[轮胎尖叫声]
- 嘿，海绵宝宝！
- Oh, not this idiot again.
- 哦，别再是这个白痴了。
- Ahhh!
- 啊啊！
[soft thud]
[轻响]
- Ah, I thought
I smelled ice cream.
- 啊，我以为
我闻到了冰淇淋的味道。
- My self-driving days
are over.
- 我的自驾时光
结束了。
- What do you plan on doing
with me, SquarePants?
- 你打算做什么
和我一起吗，方裤？
- Eh, I have an idea.
- 呃，我有一个主意。
- These self-driving boats
are real classy.
- 这些自动驾驶船
真的很优雅。
[laughing]
[笑]
[grumbles]
It stopped again.
[抱怨]
它又停了。
- Don't worry, Patrick.
- 别担心，帕特里克。
Here's a whole bag
of quarters
这是一整袋
宿舍数
so you can ride forever.
这样你就可以永远骑行。
- Ohh!
- 哦！
[exciting gibberish]
【激动人心的胡言乱语】
- Please, somebody,
strip me, sell me for parts.
- 拜托，有人，
把我剥了，卖给我换零件。
Just put me
out of my misery.
就放我吧
出于我的痛苦。